主席。
立法會主席。
They are Chapter One on management of restored landfills.
在提供詳細回覆我們的問題。
出 of the eight chapters covered by the director of orders report number seventy.
委員會已決定舉行聽證會，以檢討三個章節的細節。
On behalf of the Public Accounts Committee, I have the honour to table our report number 70 today.
我會 now highlight some of the committee's conclusions and recommendations on the chapter on integrated education.
章三， on integrated education， and chapter eight on charting section of route eight.
我們會樂意藉此機會表達對這些局和部門的感謝。
發言，梁繼昌議員就政府帳目委員會第七十號報告書向本會發言，梁繼昌議員。
委員會對這些回覆滿意，並決定無需要舉行公開聽證會討論這些章節。
委員會報告表達今日覆蓋我們的結論和建議，於章節關於統一教育。
In view of the complexity of issues raised in the other two chapters, the committee has decided to defer a full report on these two subjects.
學生有特殊教育 needs， refer to 學生， who need special educational support because of learning or adjustment difficulties.
委員會也研究了其他五個章節，由問詢相關部處提供書面回覆，回答成員對如何處理報告中提出的不足之處的問題。
for students with son.
such as direct subsidy scheme schools.
和數量學生受傷在過去五個學年。
委員會指出，有37%的增加。
under the integrated education policy adopted since 1999 to year 2000 school year.
According to the ministry's classification, there are nine categories of students with Zan.
EDB had spent more than 1.4 billion Hong Kong dollars on integrated education in that year.
consideration should also be given to allocating additional resources to help students with than in other schools.
All public sector ordinary schools are required to provide an accommodating learning environment for students with SEN.
Only students with more severe or multiple disabilities would be referred to special schools for intensive support services.
The committee urges the administration to allocate more resources to improve and expand the coverage of the measures under integrated education.
looking that EDB is currently reviewing various measures, such as the learning support grant, the intensive remedial teaching programme, and a school-based educational psychology service.
委員會表達關切，指出，經審計署報告所指的不足，反映需要更多資源，以有效實施統一教育。
在2016至2017學年，有總共超過42,000名學生在公營普通學校就讀，代表約7.8%的總學生人口在這些學校。
在 addition to regular subventions, the education bureau also provides all public sector ordinary schools with additional resources in the form of cash grant and additional teaching staff, professional support and teaching training to help schools cater.
for the learning support grant, the committee expresses serious concern that only 35 out of 277 schools have switched from an older scheme to this grant, which provides a recurrent cash grant calculated according to the number of students with.
lastly.
According to EDB.
喺呢個connection。
at a school and the required level of support.
Our gratitude also goes to the witnesses who attended the hearings.
謝偉俊議員就議事規則委員會二零一七年十月。
所有委員會的結論和建議都詳細載於報告。
自二零一八年七月嘅工作進度報告向本會發言，謝偉俊議員。多謝主持。
我 wish to record my appreciation of the contributions made by members of the committee.
學校有 reservations about the stability of the teaching force in school under the grant.
noting that this is partly attributable to the limited supply of educational psychologists.
I would also like to express our gratitude to the Director of Audit and his colleagues for their unfailing support. Thank you.
The committee expresses serious concern about inadequacies in the provision of the school-based educational psychology service.
In 2016-2017 school year, only 21% of 380 schools succeeded in the application for the enhanced service.
委員會敦促EDB，識別低切換率的原因，並考慮是否應引入新方案。
The committee urges EDB to expedite its liaison with local tertiary institutions, to increase the supply of educational psychologists, and formulate a plan to extend the enhanced service to all schools as soon as practicable.
主席本人僅以議事規則委員會主席嘅身份向本會提交。